Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Miscellaneous:
  - "In Memoriam", Mimi Benzell, Riverside Memorial Chapel, New York, 12/23/1970 (Box 71)
  - Index card, 3 x 5, lip prints (in lipstick), and one sentence in French, undated (Box 71)
  - Itinerary, mimeographed copy, 11 pages, 1959 (Box 71)
  - Loose leaf pages to scrapbooks: newspaper clippings, programs and articles, undated (Box 71)
  - Mat Numbers, "Mimi Benzell Mat Numbers", 3 pages, inside folder, undated (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, undated (Box 71)
  - Napkins, cloth, all napkins are autographed by various celebrities Mimi interviewed on her WNBC radio show; 38 pink napkins, 1 green napkin, 1965-1967 (Box 72-73)
  - Newsletters: 1, "Columbia Law School News", Volume X, No. 6; 1, "Junior High Points", Parent-Teacher Association, Weber Junior High School, attachment; 1, "WNBC 660, Local Radio in New York", "Play Ball!!", 3 copies, 01/17/1956, 05/1971 (Box 71)
  - Night Eye Shapes (used when sleeping), black, undated (Box 71)
  - Piece of Satin-like cloth (Pillowcase), pale violet with the name "Mimi" sewn in gold thread, undated (Box 71)
  - Plate, a cartoon of Mimi Benzell in costume, signed by di Benedetto, which is also engraved on the back, undated (Box 71)
  - Speech, "Good Afternoon Mrs. Henning and Friends", handwritten in ink, 4 pages, undated (Box 71)
  - Stenographer Pad, 27 pages, 1970, written by Mimi's own hand (Box 71)
  - Tablecloth, white, autographed by various celebrities that Mimi interviewed, undated (Box 71)
  - Trophy, presented to Mimi Benzell, "In Recognition of the Bond Between Us", State of Israel Bonds, Philadelphia, 10/31/1960 (Box 71)
  - Viewer, Realist Stereo, black and red, undated (Box 71)